그 자가 언제 돌아올 것 같아?
How long do you think
until he comes back?
잘 모르겠어, 곧 오겠지
I don't know.
Not long.
거의 다 된거 같아...
오, 주님!
I think I almost...
Oh, God!
어서
Come on.
넌 할 수 있어
할 수 있다구
You can do this.
손이 거의 빠진 거 같은데
- 좋아, 좋아
Almost got my hands.
Good. Good.
거의 다 됐어
- 좋아
I've almost got it.
Good.
놈이 우리 소릴 들었을까?
- 아마도..
Do you think he heard us?
I don't...
우린 괜찮을거야
I think we're okay.
우린 괜찮을거라구
I just want to see my husband.
남편이 보고 싶어
우, 해냈어, 해냈어
Ooh. I got it. I got it.
오, 주님
내가 해냈어, 오..
Oh, God.
I got it. Oh...
오, 맙소사
제발, 제발
Oh, my God.
Please. Please.
여기서 어떻게 나가지?
How do we get out of here?
잠깐, 잠깐, 잠깐만!
Wait, wait, wait!
저 박스를 이 쪽으로 가져오자
Grab that crate
and pull it over here.
좋아, 좋아, 됐어..
Okay. Okay. Let's...
좋아
됐어, 가, 가, 가, 가
Okay.
Okay. Go, go, go, go.
Quiet! Shh!
Don't make any noise.
조용! 쉬!
소리 내지 말고
Oh, my God.
오, 맙소사
이제 됐어
I got it.
Come on.
Oh, my...
서둘러
오, 이런..
어서, 서둘러
Come on. Hurry.
안돼
No.
- 안돼!
- 안 된다구..!
- No!
- No...!
오, 이런..!
Oh, G...!
오! 제발!
Oh! No!
이봐! 이봐! 이봐요! 이봐요!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
무슨 일이죠! 네?
What's going on? Huh?
You running from something?
뭔가에 쫓기고 있나요?
Yeah.
네
한 남자가 있어요
There's a man.
그 자가 우릴 납치했어요
A man took us.
911.
911입니다
네, 어떤 여자가 저희 집
옆에서 납치를 당했어요!
Yeah, some lady's being
held hostage by my house!
Lieutenant, right this way.
반장님, 이 쪽입니다
구출작전인 줄 알았는데
I thought this was
a rescue operation.
네, 그랬었죠,
근데 구조대에서 신고가 들어왔어요
Yeah, so did we. That was the
initial call from dispatch.
We must have missed him
by a few minutes.
아마 녀석을 몇분 차이로
놓친 것 같아요
And that was all...
that was needed.
그리고 남은 건..
저 것 뿐이군
자막제작 : 북극곰
S09E15 Blood Lust
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com
모두 폐쇄했습니다
It's all locked up.
좋아, 이제 집 안은 정리하도록
All right.
Let's wrap it up inside.
자네는 저 쪽을 맡게..
And let's move that
out of there...
Wonder how long he kept
놈이 희생자를 이 지하실에
얼마나 오랫동안
가두고 있었는지 궁금하군요
these women down here
in this hurricane shelter.
글쎄, 우리 생존자가
퇴원하게 되면
Well, let's hope our surviving
victim can tell us,
자세한 걸 알려주길 바래야지
when she's released
from the hospital.
Looks like she was bound with
her own belt and clothing.
희생자는 자신의
벨트와 옷으로 묶인 거 같아요
그렇군요
Okay.
나탈리아, 그게 뭔가?
Natalia, what's that?
한번 보죠
Let's see.
Look at this.
이걸 보세요
먼지하나 없이 깨끗한데요,
다른 물건들 처럼요
Doesn't have any dust on it,
like the rest of the things.
그렇다면 최근에 놓여졌다는 말이군
So it was placed here recently.
에테르군요
Ether.
덕트 테이프 랑...
Duct tape...
펜치, 방수포까지..
got pliers, a tarp...
살인도구로 알려진 것들이군
Otherwise known as a kill kit.
Yeah.
네
우리가 녀석을 방해한거에요
그래서 떠나게 된거죠
We must've interrupted him.
That's why he left it here.
사인은 질식사에요
Asphyxiation.
자기 브라로 목 졸려 죽었어요
Strangled with her own bra.
그렇다면
살인 도구를 확보한거군요
So we have
a weapon of opportunity.
Lieutenant...
반장님..
이건 일반적인 방어흔으로
보이지 않는데 말입니다
this doesn't look like
the typical defensive wound.
무슨 말씀이죠?
How do you mean?
Well, her fingernail
is pried off.
희생자의 손톱이 빠져있어요
나탈리아..
Natalia...
트렁크안에 펜치가
들어있었다고 하지 않았나?
Don't we have pliers
in that trunk?
네, 있어요
Yeah, we do.
그렇다면,
그녀는 고문을 당한거군
So, she was tortured.
저기요, 트립 형사님!
Hey, Tripp!
그래!
Yo!
What do you got?
뭐 알아낸 게 있어?
혹시 이 집 내놨다고 하지 않나요?
Do you know if this
house is for sale?
이웃집하고 얘기를 해 봤는데
Talked to the
friendly neighbor.
여기 살던 사람이 지난달에
He said the guy
that lived in here
집을 저당잡혀서는
퇴거 당했다던데
got foreclosed on
and evicted last month.
The guy sure left behind
a lot of stuff.
이 사람 확실히
많은 걸 남기고 떠났더군요
녀석이 다시 찾으러
올 거 같은가, 그러고 나선?
Think he came back for it,
and then some?
잘 모르겠어요
아마 이 살인자가
I don't know.
Looks like our killer
집에 들어가기 위해서
이 자물쇠를 이용했던 거 같아요
used the keys out of
this lock box to get in.
난 은행 담당자에게 연락해서
I'll contact the bank in charge.
관련 자료를 보내달라고 하지
Have them send the records
our way.
고맙습니다, 형사님
Thanks, Tripp.
저 사람인가?
우리 생존자 맞지?
Is this her?
So this is our survivor?
미셸 볼드윈?
Michelle Baldwin?
맞아, 법의학 간호사가 말하길
Yeah. It says here
성폭행 검사를 하기 위해서
펜타닐을 투여했다는군
the forensic nurse
had to give her fentanyl
so she could administer
the sexual assault exam.
Wow.
와우
결과는 어떻게 나왔어?
What was the result?
DNA는 발견 되지 않았어
No DNA was recovered.
녀석이 꽤 신중했나보군
Her attacker was careful.
콘돔을 썼나봐
He wore a condom.
그래
Okay.
미셸씨?
- 네
Michelle?
Yeah.
안녕하세요
Hi.
전 나탈리아 보아 비스타라고 합니다
I'm Natalia Boa Vista.
This is Ryan Wolfe.
이 분은 라이언 울프씨구요
놈을 잡으셨나요?
Did you catch him?
아, 아뇨, 아직 못 잡았습니다
Uh, no. We have not
caught him yet.
하지만 당신이 기억해 내신다면
우리가 쫓는데 도움이 될 겁니다
But we're hoping your memories
can help us track him down.
제-제가 지금 좀 혼란스러워서요
My-my mind is just
really scrambled up
지금은, 잘 모르겠어요..
right now, I don't...
그건 아주 자연스러운 외상입니다
That's very normal with trauma.
그러니, 걱정마세요
저희가 생각을 정리하시게끔
So, don't worry,
we're going to help you
도와드리겠습니다
- 네
try to sort all this out.
Okay.
미셸씨, 혹시 얼마나 오랫동안
Michelle, do you remember
how long you were
지하실에 갇혀 있었는지
기억나시나요?
in that hurricane shelter for?
네, 어젯밤 부터요
Yes. Just since last night.
하지만 다른 여자, 브리짓은..
But the other girl, Bridgette...
저한테 말하길
she told me
그 곳에 몇일 동안
갇혀 있었다고 하더라고요
that she had been down there
for days.
Did Bridgette ever tell you
her last name?
혹시 브리짓씨가
성은 안 알려주던가요?
월시요
Walsh;
브리짓 월시요
Bridgette Walsh.
그 친구는 미혼이에요
근데 개를 기른다더군요
She wasn't married,
but she had a dog.
개 이름은 벨이고
라브래도 종이랬어요
She had a...
Labrador named Belle.
자기 개가 걱정된다고
계속 저한테 얘기 하더라고요
She kept saying
she was really worried
about... the dog.
벨이 잘 있나 확인했어야 하는데
I should go check on Belle.
잘 있는지 확실히 가 봤어야..
I should go make sure she's
got...
있잖아요, 음식하고..
물 같은거요..
you know, food and...
water, and...
Well, I-I promise you
음, 저희가 벨이 잘 있는지
꼭 확인하도록 할게요
we'll make sure
that Belle is okay.
하지만 지금은
미셸씨에게 집중하자구요
But let's just focus on you
right now.
제가 보기에 브리짓씨를 위해
할 수 있는 최선은
I-I think the best thing
that you could do for Bridgette
미셸씨가 알고 있는 걸 모두 다
저희와 공유하는 것일거에요
would be to try to share
as much of your story with us
as you can.
어, 미셸씨, 혹시 당신을
Uh, Michelle, I was wondering
지하실에 가두었던 남자의
신체적 특징을 기억하고 계신가요?
if you could remember any
physical characteristics
of the person who put you in
that storm shelter.
전 장님이었어요, 그게..
I was blindfolded. I mean, I...
I know. I wish that there
was another way.
알아요,
뭔가 다른 방법이 있겠죠
이해해요
- 네
There... I do.
Okay.
Well, he was strong.
글쎄요, 놈은 강했어요
정말 힘이 셌어요
그건 확실해요
He was really strong.
I know that much.
제 자신이 너무..
I just felt so...
제 자신이 초라하게 느껴졌어요
I just, I felt so small.
그래요, 미..
- 아뇨!
Okay, Mi...
No!
그만! 그만요
- 괜찮아요
Don't! Don't.
It's okay.
이제 괜찮아요
이봐요, 걱정하지 마세요
It's all right.
Look, don't worry. Don't worry.
우리랑 있으니 안전해요, 약속해요
우리랑 있으면 안전하다고요
You're safe here with us, I promise
you, you are safe here now.
브리짓이랑 창문으로 나올 때
먼저 내보내 줬어야 했는데
I should've let Bridgette
go out the window first.
브리짓이 먼저 도망쳤어야 했어요
She should've been
the first to go.
미셸, 지하실에 있었던 일은
당신의 탓이 아니에요
Michelle, nothing that happened
in that hurricane shelter
was your fault,
그리고 거기서
할 수 있는 것도 없었구요
or had anything to do with you.
미셸!
Michelle!
오, 맙소사!
Oh, my God!
정말 미안해
I'm so sorry.
Mr. Baldwin?
볼드윈 선생님?
네, 데니스요
Yeah. Dennis.
전 어젯밤에 사업차
탤러해시에 있었어요
I was in Tallahassee,
on business last night.
아내가 체크인을 안해서
걱정이 많았어요
Started to worry when she didn't
check in. You know what?
난 그냥 당신이 TV보다가
잠든 줄만 알았어
I thought that you were
watching TV,
and fallen asleep.
Just please take me home.
빨리 집에 가자
볼드윈씨, 괜찮으시면 부인께
몇가지 질문을 더 해도 될런지요
Mr. Baldwin, we'd like to ask
your wife
a few more questions, if
that's all right. I can't.
못하겠어요
지금은 못하겠어요
죄송해요
I just can't.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
'Cause I have to go home.
괜찮아
- 단지 집에 가고 싶을 뿐이요
괜찮습니다
- 그럼 다음에 하는 건 어떨까요?
It's okay.
Why don't we do this then?
괜찮으시면 다음 번에 의사와의
상담을 예약해 드리는 건 어떨까요
How about if we set up
a session with
one of our therapists,
for later? All right.
That's fine.
좋아요, 그렇게 해요
어서 가자
- 그래, 그래, 가자
Let's go.
Okay. Okay, let's go.
How'd it go
with Michelle Baldwin?
미셸 볼드윈은 어때?
글쎄..
Well...
불쌍한 여자에게
엄청난 일이 닥쳐버린거지
that poor woman has got
a whole lot of work
ahead of her.
정신적 충격을 받은거지
게다가 생존자 자책에도 빠져버렸어
She's traumatized,
and she's got survivor guilt
on top of that.
이 일에서 보람이 하나 있다면
You learn anything
in this business,
그런 사람들이 회복돼가는걸
보는 거란 말이지
it's that people are resilient.
So she'll bounce back.
그녀도 그렇게 될거야
Yeah.
응
What do you have there?
그 쪽은 어때?
저당잡힌 집에 대한 정보야?
Is that the information on
the foreclosure of the house?
응, 마이애미 유나이티드가
소유하고 있어
Yeah. Miami United
owns the property.
They haven't heard a peep
from the ex-owner.
그 사람들은 전 주인의 출현에
대해선 들어본적이 없다는군
확실히, 저당에서
풀리니 기뻐하더구만
Apparently, he was happy
to walk away from the mortgage.
Who had access to the lock box?
자물쇠에 접근할 수 있는 사람은?
은행에서 그 일을 맡고 있는 남자
Guy who was in charge of the
case for the bank,
휴 파커야
Hugh Parker.
네, 사무실로 연락드리죠
Yes, I will call the office.
오, 파커씨, 부탁하셨던
Oh, Mr. Parker, um,
this is the notice of default
채무불이행 통지서입니다
you asked me for.
오, 카일라
Oh, Kayla.
내가 말했었잖아, 프랜시스 가라구
해링턴이라구 썼잖아
I told you. Francis Street.
This is Harrington.
죄-죄송해요, 확실히 해링턴이라고
하셨던 거 같았는데요
I'm-I'm sorry. I could have sworn
that you said "Harrington."
근데, 내가 안 그랬어, 알겠지?
Well, I didn't, okay?
사무실에 다른 사람이
똑바로 전해주겠지
Have someone at the office
get the right one for me.
서둘러, 어서
가, 가라구
Quickly. Come on,
let's go. Let's go.
주인이 12시까지 가져달라고 하니까
- 휴 파커씨? 휴 파커씨?
The owners need it in hand by noon.
Hugh Parker? Hugh Parker?
네, 네, 이 집에서 살인 사건이
났다는 전화를 받았어요
Yeah. Yeah. I got a call
about a crime at this property?
We need to talk to
you alone, please.
선생 한 분과만 얘기를
좀 해야겠습니다
Go. Go.
가도 돼, 가
파커씨, 누군가가
선생의 자물쇠를 열고
Mr. Parker, somebody
accessed your lock box,
집에 들어가서는
한 여자를 죽였어요
entered the home,
and killed a woman here.
Officers, you have
to understand,
경관님, 이해해 주셔야겠지만
전 73개의 소유지를
관리하고 있습니다
I'm supervising 73 properties.
집을 보여달라는 중개인을
모두 다 만날 순 없다구요
I can't meet every broker
that wants to show one.
뭐요? 그러면 암호를
막 알려준다는 겁니까?
What? Do you just
give them the code?
네, 그럼요
Yeah. Exactly.
Seems to me anybody could call
요즘은 아무나 부동산 중개인인
척 하면서 연락해 오는걸요
and pretend
to be a real estate agent.
Mr. Parker, who called
on the Oak Street?
파커씨, 오크가는
누가 담당했었죠?
열 댓명 정도 돼요
Dozens of people.
But I'm sure Kayla
하지만 카일라는 제대로 하지 않은 거 같더군요
didn't keep track.
그녀의 기록 보존은
미진한 점이 많아요
Her record-keeping leaves
a lot to be desired.
네, 기록 보존이나 하라고
그녀를 고용한 거 같진 않은데요
Yeah. I didn't think you
hired her for record-keeping.
오늘 아침에는 어디 계셨죠, 파커씨?
Where were you this morning,
Mr. Parker?
I went to the office early.
일찍 사무실에 나왔어요
대출 문서를 찾느라
문서고에 들어가 있었죠
Logged some time in the archive
room, looking for loan docs.
확인해 줄 사람이 있습니까?
Can anyone confirm that?
네, 카일라도 거기 있었어요
절 봤죠
Yeah. Kayla was there.
She saw me.
참 편하군요
How convenient.
You know,
I'm sure Kayla can confirm
근데, 카일라씨는
당신이 확인해 달라하면
뭐든지 다 확인해주겠죠, 그렇죠?
just about whatever
you tell her to confirm, right?
트렁크에는 지문이 하나도 없어요
The trunk came up
totally empty for prints.
내용물은요?
What about its contents?
옷가지하고 덕트 테이프는
흔히 널린 것들이라서요
These rags and duct tape
are about
as generic as they come.
마이애미의 어느 철물점에서든
다 구할 수 있는 것들이에요
Available at any hardware store
in Miami.
네, 저도 운이 별로
없는 것 같지만요, 어..
Yeah. I'm not having
much luck, either. Uh...
브리짓 월시는 일주일 전에
Bridgette Walsh was
last seen outside her gym
그녀의 체육관 밖에서
마지막으로 목격 됐어요
about a week ago.
그리고 그녀와 미셸 사이에서는
어떠한 연결점도 찾지 못했구요
And I can't find any connection
between her and Michelle.
음, 미셸은 요가 강사가 아니었나요?
Well, isn't Michelle
a yoga instructor?
그녀가 브리짓의 체육관에서
일했던 게 아닐까요?
Did she work at Bridgette's gym?
그것도 꽤나 좋은 이론이군요
That's actually
a pretty good theory,
아쉽지만 아니에요,
둘 다 도시의 정반대편에 있고
but no, they're from
different sides of town
공통의 친구도 갖고 있지 않아요
and they don't have
any friends in common.
글쎄요, 그래도 뭔가 있을거에요
Well, there's
got to be something.
어서 이 녀석을
잡아야 할텐데 말이죠
We need to take
this guy off the street.
반갑구나
Hello.
What is that?
그게 뭐죠?
Appears to be a
piece of a wing,
어떤 날개 조각처럼 생겼는데요
나비일 가능성이 높아요
possibly a butterfly.
어떤 종인지 아세요?
Do you know what species?
육안으로만요?
By eyeballing it?
그 정도는 아니에요
I'm not that good.
좋아
All righty.
아니, 그건 아니에요
No, not that one.
그거요, 그거에요
There, that one.
무늬가 같군요
Looks like the same design.
Cyclargus thomasi
사이클라구스 토마시
베튠베커리에요
bethunebakeri.
More commonly known
as the Miami Blue.
마애이미 블루로 흔히 알려져있죠
자료에 따르면, 이건 오직 포트셔먼
주립공원에서만 발견된다는군요
According to this, found only
in Fort Sherman State Park.
이 쪽으로!
Over here!
뭔가 좀 찾았나요?
Did you find anything?
이 쪽을 봐요!
Look over here!
어서, 서둘러, 서둘러!
Come on, let's go! Let's go!
가자, 가자!
Let's go, let's go!
저기요, 반장님?
Hey, H?
You're gonna want to see this.
이걸 좀 봐주셔야 될 거 같은데요
Someone was planning
a private burial.
누군가 사유 무덤을 만들려했군
You think this was made
for Bridgette and Michelle?
이게 브리짓과 미셸을
위한 거라고 보시나요?
그런 것 같네
I do.
반장님, 미셸은 도망쳤고, 놈은
브리짓도 여기로 못 끌고 왔는데요
H, Michelle got away, and he never
got a chance to drag Bridgette here.
여기 초목을 보게
Look at this vegetation.
누군가 여기에 묻힌 거 같아요
There's someone else
buried here.
그렇다면 브리짓이 놈의
첫번째 희생자가 아닌거군요
So Bridgette wasn't
his first victim.
그렇네
No.
우린 말이지..
연쇄 살인범을 상대하는거야
We're dealing...
with a serial killer.
Her extremities have been
bound with clothing, like before.
시신의 사지가 옷으로 묶여 있어,
이전의 시신처럼 말야
The killer used the victim's
own bra to strangle her.
살인자는 그녀의 브라로
목을 졸라 죽였고 말야
브리짓 월시 처럼요?
Just like Bridgette Walsh?
저기요, 박사님
Hey, Tom.
Look at how Ryan's
holding his shovel.
라이언이 삽 들고 있는것 좀 보세요
Hey, Tom.
근데요, 박사님
라이언이 어떻게 이 삽질을
혼자 다하고 있는지도 좀 보세요
Also make a note of how Ryan's
doing all
the shoveling by himself.
I mean, look
how he's holding it.
제 말은, 라이언이 삽을
어떻게 들고 있는 지 말이에요
He's got his hand all the way
to the very end for leverage.
라이언의 손을 항상
삽자루 끝부분을 잡고 있죠
So?
Now look at this.
그래서?
- 이제 이걸 보세요
The shovel we found
at the gravesite.
무덤에서 발견한 삽이에요
The muddy handprints
on this shovel
삽 위의 진흙에 묻어 있는 지문은 삽 머리 근처에 집중되어 있군
are focused at this
end, near the spade.
How I would hold it.
제가 어떻게 들고 있나 보세요
A girl.
이건 여자에요
A woman dug that grave.
여자가 무덤을 판 거군
He made his first victim
dig her own grave.
살인자는 자신의 첫 희생자에게
스스로 무덤을 파게 만든거야
We got an I.D. on that
girl from the grave.
무덤에서 꺼낸 시신의
신원을 확인했어
Allison Caldwell, 26.
앨리슨 칼드웰, 26세야
Reported missing two weeks ago
그녀가 웨이트리스로 일하던
레스토랑에서 2주 전에
실종 신고가 들어왔어
from the restaurant
where she was a waitress.
그녀 역시 다른 희생자 처럼
손톱이 사라졌어
She's also got the same
signature missing fingernail
as the other victims.
Maybe it wasn't
어쩌면 우리가 생각하는 것처럼
고문 도구 때문은 아닐지도 몰라
a torture device
like we thought.
어쩌면 살인자가
기념품으로 가져갔던지
Maybe the killer was taking a
memento, something to revisit
살인현장에 재방문 했을수도 있어
the murder.
I don't understand why this time
왜 하필 한 번에 두 명의
사람을 죽였는 지 이해가 안돼
he had two victims at once.
아마 우울함을
떨쳐내기 위함일거야
Probably was trying
to stave off depression.
What do you mean?
Serial killers experience a high,
그게 무슨 뜻이야?
연쇄살인범들은 대개 자기가
납치한 사람에게 더 이상 흥미를
followed by a low
when they realize
끌지 못하면 다른 사냥감을
찾게 되는 법이지
they no longer have
anyone to toy with.
그래서 놈이 첫번째 희생자가
아직 지하실에 살아 있을 때
So he kidnaps his second victim
while his first victim's
두번째 희생자를 납치했다는 거야?
still alive in the shelter?
Yeah.
응
Okay, well, maybe
we can stop that pattern.
좋아, 어쩌면 우리가
그 패턴을 멈출 수 있을거야
Look at this.
이거 봐라
What'd you find?
DNA.
뭐 좀 찾았어?
- DNA야
In the form of a pubic hair.
음모 모양이군
Let's see if we can find
out who this belongs to.
이게 누구 껀지 찾아봐야지
Art Gelway.
아트 켈웨이
그런데요
Yeah.
Table 19.
19번 테이블이야
Uh, wh-what's this about?
어, 뭐-뭐 때문에 그러시죠?
앨리슨 칼드웰 때문이네
Allison Caldwell.
We found
오늘 아침에
그녀의 시신을 발견했어
her body this morning.
뭐라구요?
What?
앨리슨이 죽었어요?
She's dead?
응, 죽었어
Yeah, she's dead.
그녀는 또한 여기 웨이트리스였구
And she was also
a waitress here.
그녀에게서 당신의 털을
We found your DNA on her
발견했는데 두 번의
친밀한 관계가 있으셨더군
that suggests the two of you
had an intimate relationship.
또 전과도 있더구만
And it turns out
that you have a record.
미성년자 강간이었어요
Statutory rape.
몇 년전 일이라구요
Years ago.
제가 18살 때
고등학생 여자친구가 있었는데
All right?
The result of me turning 18
걔네 아빠가
절 엿먹인거라구요
before my high school girlfriend
and her father being a jerk.
저건 트리샤에요
That's Tricia.
몇년 동안 사귀었죠
We've been together
for over a year now.
But you've been
with Allison, too?
근데 앨리슨과도 그랬었지?
네, 됐어요?
Yes. Okay?
아.. 몇 주전에
저희는, 어, 알다시피,
A... few weeks back,
we, uh, you know,
좀 서먹해졌었어요
split a bottle of cab.
Wait.
잠깐만
What about Tricia?
트리샤는 어쩌구?
What she doesn't know
won't kill her.
그녀가 뭘 알겠어?
One thing led to another,
you know...
말 안해도 아시겠죠,
알다시피...
So you were cheating
on your girlfriend?
그래서 여자친구
냅두고 바람 핀건가?
Once, okay?
딱 한번이었어요, 네?
It was a mistake.
그건 실수였다구요
It also provided you
그게 자네에게 동기부여가
된 거 같은데, 아트
with motive, Art.
You were afraid Allison
would tell Tricia.
앨리슨이 트리샤에게
말할 까봐 걱정된 거군
Where were you this morning?
오늘 아침엔 어딨었나?
Here.
여기요
Prepping this bar
for the lunchtime rush.
점심시간 준비하느라
정신 없었어요
혼자 있었나?
You the only one?
Yeah, so?
네, 그래서요?
이거 하는데
몇 사람이나 필요하겠어요?
How many guys
you think it takes?
So another girl named Bridgette
Walsh got killed this morning.
오늘 아침에 살해된
브리짓 월시라는 여자가 있는데
우린 앨리슨 칼드웰을 죽인 자와
동일인이라고 보고 있어
And we think it was the same guy
that killed Allison Caldwell.
울프군, 저 그릇은 오늘 아침에
범죄 현장에서 본 거 같지 않나?
Mr.
Wolfe, weren't those the containers
from the crime scene?
We do a lot of takeout business.
저희는 테이크 아웃 전문이에요
지난 달에 나온
영수증을 다 봐야겠네
I'm gonna need the receipts
for the last month.
이 자는 앨하우스의 바텐더에요
This man's a
bartender at the Ale House.
He look familiar?
낯이 익으신가요?
According to the receipts,
you got food there last night.
영수증을 보니 어젯밤에
거기서 음식을 구입하셨더군요
Is that the guy?
이게 그 남잔가요?
그 사람 중 하나...
절 잡은 사람인가요?
Is he the one that...
that grabbed me?
One of the other
다른 피해자는 거기에서 일하던
웨이트리스 였습니다
victims was a waitress
who worked there.
이름은 앨리슨 칼드웰이구요
Her name was Allison Caldwell.
We found her body
저희가 어제 포트 셔먼 공원에
묻혀 있던 그녀의 시신을 찾았습니다
buried at Fort Sherman
State Park.
I remember I walked out
of the restaurant, and I...
레스토랑에서 나왔던 게
기억나요, 그리고 전..
I had the food
손에 음식을 들고 있었고
골목길을 걸어 내려왔어요
그리고는..
in my hand, and I went down
the alleyway and...
그러는데 누군가가 와서는..
누군가가 제 뒤로 다가와서는..
And then someone came...
someone came up behind me and
and... and grabbed me
절 붙잡았어요
제.. 제 머리카락을요
by my... by my hair.
그리고 힘이 너무..
And the force was...
너무 세서 음식을 바닥에..
떨어뜨리고 말았어요..
was so much that the food
got on-on the ground,
그리고..
and...
And then, there was this cloth
그리고는.. 헝겊 같은 걸로
제 입을 틀어막았어요
that he put over my mouth.
정말 끔찍한 경험이었고..
It-It tasted horrible, and..
전 숨도 쉴 수 없었어요
I couldn't breathe.
Yeah, that was the
ether that knocked you
네, 당신을 기절시킨 건
에테르 였어요
unconscious.
네, 그런 거 같아요,
그리고는,
Yeah, that makes sense,
because then,
제 기억에 전부 다 그냥..
I remember
everything just got...
전부 캄캄해 졌어요
Everything went black.
그리고, 제가 일어났을 때
And then, when I woke up,
전 눈이 가려진 채로
지하실에 갇혀 있었죠
I was in the shelter,
and I had the blindfold.
아니, 아니, 아니
됐어, 됐어, 그만해
And... No, no, no.
No, no, that's okay.
이제 괜찮아,
당신은 이제 집에 있어, 괜찮지?
It's okay.
You're home now, all right? Okay?
여기까지만 해주시면 안 될까요?
Is-Is that gonna be
all for now?
네, 충분한 거 같군요
Yeah, I think we have enough.
협조해 주셔서 정말 고맙습니다
Thank you very much
for your help.
네, 알겠습니다
Yeah, that's all right.
Our missing woman
is Wendy Gibson.
실종 여성은 웬디 깁슨이야
She works here at
the flower shop.
여기 꽃 가게에서 일하던 여자구
Any idea when she was taken?
그녀가 납치된 때는요?
Yeah, about an hour ago.
응, 한 시간 전 쯤이야
목격자가 비명소리를 들었고,
자동차가 떠나는 걸 봤대
Witness heard her scream,
and saw the car drive off.
Patrol found this ether rag.
순찰 경관이
이 에테르 조각을 발견했어
미셸과 같은 수법이군
Same MO as Michelle.
와우, 백주 대낮에
여자를 납치해 가다니
Wow. She was taken
in broad daylight.
This guy is getting bolder.
정말 대담한 녀석이군요
"녀석들"이라고 해야 맞을거 같은데
I think you
mean "they."
What?
뭐라구요?
목격자가 얼굴을 보진 못했지만
Witness didn't see any faces,
차 안에 남자와 여자가
타고 있는 걸 봤다더군
but said there was a man
and a woman in the car.
남자와 여자라
A man and a woman.
그렇다면 커플을 찾으면 되겠군
So we're looking for a couple.
Hey, this is kind of
extreme, isn't it?
이봐요,
좀 과격한 거 같은데요, 네?
납치와 살인 말하는건가?
Murder and kidnapping?
It's about
니가 한 짓은 어떻고 말야,
바보 멍충아
as extreme
as you can get, dumbass.
What?!
뭐요?!
아틀란타로 가는 편도 기차표를
끊은 사실을 알고 있어
We know about the one-way
train tickets to Atlanta.
도망이라도 가려고 그래?
What were you running for?
If Wendy Gibson is still alive,
웬디 깁슨이 아직 살아있다면,
사형 집행 당하는 건
막아줄 수 있어
I can prevent you from receiving
a lethal injection.
잠시만요, 웬디 누구요?
Wait. Wendy who?
그만두지
Stop it.
당신 지문을 조사해 봤어
We ran your prints.
트리샤 큄비로 행세하고 있는
You're going
by the name Tricia Quimby,
당신의 실명은 트리샤 잭슨이지
but your real name's
Tricia Jackson.
당신과 남자 공범은 절도 혐의로
You and a male accomplice
took a robbery charge
애리조나에서 2년을 살았더구만
two years ago in Arizona.
그리고 마이애미에 새로운
파트너를 찾으러 왔구 말야
And you came down to Miami
to select a new partner.
아뇨, 사실,
전 손 씻었어요, 네?
No. Actually,
I've been clean, okay?
전 다시 시작하려고
노력하고 있다구요
I'm trying to start over,
do things right this time.
If Wendy Gibson is not alive,
웬디 깁슨이 만약 죽었으면
you're both going to regret it.
자네들 둘 다 후회하게 될거야
납치 용의자가 구금 중에 있으나
Kidnapped suspects
are in custody,
피해자의 행방을
계속 수색중이다
but we're still looking
for the whereabouts
of the victim.
웬디 깁슨이란 이름의
흑인 여성으로 나이는 30세이다
Name Wendy Gibson,
African-American female
30 years of age.
Hey, Tripp?
저기요, 형사님?
What do you got?
뭐 나왔어?
You said Wendy Gibson
worked here, right?
웬디 깁슨이 여기 일한다고 했었죠?
Yeah, sales manager. Why?
응, 판매 담당자로, 왜?
She must have dropped these
when she was kidnapped.
그녀가 납치 됐을 때
이걸 떨어뜨린 거 같아서요
이 꽃들 사이에 말이군
- 네, 근데
Along with those flowers.
Yeah, but
check this out.
이걸 한번 보세요
There's some of
that fake grass.
인조 잔디가 좀 섞여 있는데요
See it?
Yeah, but this place
보이세요?
- 응, 근데 이 장소는
뭐 지구의 날 행사 장소도 아니고
완전 푸르디 푸른데
is an all-natural, all-green,
Earth Day kind of place.
Exactly, so maybe one of our
killers tracked it over here.
확실히, 용의자 중 한명이 이걸
붙이고 온 게 분명해요
The blades from the floral shop
꽃 가게에서 가져온 잎은
폴리프로필렌과
나일론이에요
are polypropylene and nylon.
캔터키블루그래스을
모방해서 염색한 것이죠
Dyed to mimic
Kentucky Blue Grass.
그렇다면 화학 성분 구성과
So I'm guessing the exact
chemical composition
색은 마음대로 바꿀 수
있다는 거군요, 그렇죠? - 네
and color vary among
manufacturers, right? Yes.
그리고 전 이것들이 휴스턴에 있는
공장에서 나왔다는 걸 찾았어요
And I was able to trace these
back to a factory in Houston.
판매부서에서 분명히 그들이
The sales department should be
sending me a list
지역업자에게 판매한
목록이 있을거에요
of all the local contractors
they sold to.
오, 여기 있네요
Oh, and here it is.
If we can find out
만약 그들이 최근에 잔디를
판매한 집을 찾을 수 있다면
which homes they've sold
the grass to recently,
단서를 찾을 수 있겠죠
we might have a lead.
전화를 걸 때가 왔군요
Time to start making
some phone calls.
Hey, nice work, Molly.
정말 멋진데요, 몰리
Hey, check
for bank-seized homes.
저기, 은행에 잡혀 있는
집을 확인해봐요
The women this morning--
오늘 아침에 발견된 여자가
그 저당잡힌 집에 있었어요
they were held
in foreclosed homes.
웬디?
Wendy?
웬디 깁슨씨?
Wendy Gibson.
안돼요, 제발
절 해치지 마세요, 제발
No, please.
Please don't hurt me, please.
괜찮아요, 아가씨
It's all right, sweetheart.
우린 경찰입니다
We're the police.
당신을 구하러 왔어요
I'm just gonna turn
you over slowly.
진정, 진정, 진정하세요
Easy. Easy, easy.
이봐요, 웬디,
어디 아픈데 없어요?
Hey. Wendy,
are you hurt?
그들이 어디 갔는지 모르겠어요
I don't know where they went.
전.. 전 무슨 약을 맞았는데
I was... I was drugged
with something,
그들이 뭐라고 하는 걸 들었어요
but I-I think I heard them...
그녀를 묶어.. 묶어
Tie her up... Tie her up...
저 여잔 죽어야 돼
She has to die.
그녀가 자초한거야
She asked for it.
그녀가 초래한 거라구
She brought this on herself.
어쨌든 간에..
어쨌든 우릴 보호해야해
Whatever it takes...
whatever it takes to protect us.
제가 깨어났을 때, 앞이 안 보였어요
- 걱정마세요
- But when I woke up, I was blindfolded.
- Don't worry.
괜찮아요, 우리가 온 지
한 시간 정도 됐어요
It's okay. We got 'em both
about an hour ago.
아니, 아니, 안돼요
그건 불가능해요
No. No, no, no,
that's not possible.
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이죠?
They only left
a few minutes ago.
그 사람들 떠난지 몇 분 안 됐어요
당신들이 와서 도망간 거 같아요
I think you scared them away.
방금전까지 있었다고요
They were just here.
Horatio?
Mm-hmm.
반장님?
- 음흠
웬디는 아트와 트리샤를
알아보지 못 했어요
Wendy can't positively
ID Art or Tricia.
Have you followed up
with the house, Frank?
그 집에 대해선 알아봤나, 프랭크?
Owners defaulted
on their mortgage.
소유자가 대출금을 연체했다더군
Miami United owns it now.
지금은 마이애미
유나이티드로 넘어갔구
저당업무 담당자가 누구지?
And guess who's in charge
of the foreclosure?
휴 파커일세
- 알았어
Hugh Parker.
Yup.
Is that the same
guy who had access
오늘 아침에 그 집에 들어 갔던
사람과 같은 남자죠?
to the house this morning?
Yeah.
응, 그 자와 비서가 서로
감싸주고 있는 게 틀림 없어
He and his secretary could be
covering for each other.
그들을 데려와주게
Bring them in, please.
그들이 부인하면요?
What if they deny it?
생존자와 얘길해 봐야겠지
Talk to the survivor.
So, you killed Allison
Caldwell and Bridgette Walsh.
그래서, 당신이 앨리슨 칼드웰과
브리짓 월시를 죽인거죠
I'm not gonna sit here
and listen to these accusations.
더 이상 여기 앉아서
그런 비난을 들을 수 없군요
앉으시지
당신은 어디도 갈 수 없소
Sit down.
You're not going anywhere.
미셸?
Michelle?
나탈리아 보아 비스타입니다,
마이애미 경찰이에요
Natalia Boa Vista, MDPD.
우리가 이걸 찾았어요,
어, 당신 사무실에서요
We found these,
uh, in your office.
That's just part
of a game we play.
이건 우리가 즐기는
게임의 일부일 뿐입니다
이게.. 게임의 일부라구요?
Is this... part of the game?
Kayla, was there
카일라, 당신이 참여한
또 다른 게임이 있나요
any other games he had
you participate in?
Like what?
이를테면요?
이보세요?
- 잘 모르지만,
Do you mind?
I don't know,
두 명의 여자가 죽고
like ending the
lives of two women
또 다른 두 사람을
납치하는 그런거 말이죠
and abducting two others.
Hey.
안녕하세요
죄송해요, 아직 상담치료사와
약속을 못 잡았어요
I'm sorry, I haven't made
that therapist appointment yet.
아직은 그럴 기분이 아니라서요
I just haven't really felt
up to it.
신경쓰지 마세요,
오늘 제가 온 이유는
That's okay, but I do really
need your help, and I was
사진 한 장만 더 봐 주실 수
있을 까 해서에요
wondering if you could look
at one more picture for me.
몇 분이면 될 거에요
It'll only take a minute.
고마워요
Thanks.
Horatio.
반장님
So I, uh, I processed
Wendy Gibson's bindings
제가, 어, 웬디를 묶었던
줄을 검사하고 있는 중에
이 털을 찾았는데,
웬디꺼라고 하기엔 너무 밝고
and I found this, but this
is too light to be Wendy's
남자꺼라고 하기엔
너무 길단 말이죠
and too long to be a man's.
Could it be from the accomplice?
공범의 것일 수도 있지 않은가?
You know what?
그럼 말이지?
Let's run it for Kayla Hammond.
카일라 해몬드 것을 돌려보도록
Got it.
알겠습니다
제가 살인자라고 보시나요, 네?
You think I'm a murderer, too?
우린 커플을 찾고 있어요
We're looking for a couple.
Mr. Parker wasn't
in the file room
파커씨는 오늘 아침
자기가 말한 것처럼
문서고에 있지 않았어요
that morning
like he said he was.
Kayla.
카일라
오, 정말요?
Oh, really?
그럼, 도대체 어디에 계셨단거요?
Well, where the hell was he?
He was at my place,
저희 집에 왔었어요
just like he is every morning.
매일 아침 그랬던 것처럼요
Okay.
좋아요
There you have it.
I'm banging my secretary,
이제 털어놓을게요
전 비서와 놀아나긴 했지만
but I didn't kill anyone.
아무도 죽이진 않았어요
이제 가도 되나요?
- 아뇨, 아직은요
- Can we go now?
- No, you can't go.
당신들 두 명만이
희생자가 잡혀 있던
The two of you are the
only ones with access
집에 들어갈 수 있는
권한이 있기 때문이에요
to both houses where
the victims were held.
그리고 알리바이도 서로에게
밖에는 확인이 안되구요
And your only alibi
is still each other.
What did you say this guy's
이 남자의 이름이
뭐라고 하셨었죠?
name was again?
휴 파커요
Hugh Parker.
보신적이 있나요?
Does he look familiar?
I'm sorry, I... I
really don't know.
죄송하지만,
저..전 정말 모르겠어요
Maybe.
어쩌면요
제 말은,
혹시 지난번에 아트라는
I mean, didn't you
say you were looking
이름을 가진 누군가를
찾는다고 하지 않았었나요?
for someone named
Art last time?
Are you any closer at all
to finding this killer?
지금쯤은 살인자 근처에라도
가 있어야 하는거 아닌가요?
How many more victims
are going to...?
얼마나 더 많은 희생자가...?
죄송해요
- 당신 잘못이 아녜요
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
어, 이거 이상한데요
Uh, this is weird.
머리카락이 대조 샘플의
DNA와 일치하는군요
The hair DNA matches
a control sample.
하지만 샘플은 피해자의
강간 테스트용 밖에는 없는 데 말이야
But we only did rape kits
on the victims.
Apparently not.
확실히 아니군요
나탈리아
Natalia.
We're out of paper towels.
I'll be right back.
휴지가 다 떨어졌네요
금방 돌아올게요
기다리세요, 바로 갈게요
Hold on, I'll be right there.
What the hell do you think
you're doing, huh?
도대체 무슨 짓을 하려는 거야, 응?
자기, 자기, 여기 있어
Baby, baby, get in here.
Babe, I caught her
자기야,
이 여자가 어슬렁 거리는 걸
내가 잡았어
sniffing around.
What do we do?
이제 어쩔까?
우리가 만약 체포되면,
If we get arrested,
그들이 우릴 갈라놓을거야
they're going to separate us.
여자를 제거 해야만 해
We have to get rid of her.
이건 좋은 생각이 아니에요
That's really not a good idea.
일단 그 총 좀
내려 놓는게 어때요?
Why don't you just
put the gun down?
We can totally
talk this through.
차근차근히 대화를 해봐요
무슨 일이 있었는지
이해하고 싶어요
I'd actually like
to understand what happened.
그, 그가 당신 몰래
바람이라도 피웠나요?
Was, was he cheating
on you with these women?
Of course not,
but he would have.
물론 아니죠,
하지만 그럴지도 몰라요
데니스는 아주 강력하고
도발적인 매력이 있어요
Dennis has a very
powerful sexual aura.
Mm-hmm, it's hard work
음흠, 결혼생활을 유지하는 것도
보통 일이 아니지
- 그래
keeping a marriage together.
Mm-hmm,
그 웨이트리스처럼 말이지
like that waitress.
Here you go.
여습니다
고마워요
Thank you.
천만에요
- 고맙습니다
You're welcome.
Thank you.
음, 사실 전 여기 처음이라서요
Um, I'm actually
on the fence here.
What do you recommend,
추천하는 메뉴가 있나요?
앨리슨?
Allison?
일단 이 메뉴를 추천드리고요,
I would recommend this one, and
제가 가장 좋아하는 건
이 메뉴입니다
this one's my favorite
right here.
This one's good right here?
이게 가장 좋다고요?
음흠, 네, 그게 가장 멋진 메뉴에요
- 좋아요
Mm-hmm, yeah, that's a
really good one. Okay.
She was trying to lure him
away, but we didn't let her.
그 여자가 남편을 꼬실려고 했지만,
가만히 내버려 두지 않았죠
안돼요
No.
저 여잔 더이상 당신을
괴롭히지 못할거야, 베이비
She can't hurt you
anymore, baby.
정말 사랑해, 여보
I love you so much, baby.
So, what was
the whole escape thing about?
그러면,
그 탈출 시도는 어떻게 된거지?
그것도 계획의 일부였나?
Why-- was that part
of the plan?
Were you just supposed
to run around
왜 굳이 집 밖으로
도망쳐 나왔던거지?
the back of the house?
탈출은 최고의 장면이지
The escape was the best part.
You can do it.
할 수 있어
할 수 있어, 할 수 있다구
You can do it, you can do it.
I've almost got it now.
거의 다 된 것 같아
오, 제발
- 거의 다 됐어
Oh, come on.
I've almost got it.
할 수 있어, 넌 할 수 있어
- 거의 됐어, 거의
You can do it, you can do it.
I'm trying, I'm trying.
어서, 어서
Come on, come on.
Take your belt off.
벨트를 풀어
Take your belt off right...!
당장 벨트 풀지 못해..!
뒤로 돌아
Turn around.
When those women
fixate on Dennis,
여자들이 데니스를 응시할 때
they get this look
in their eyes,
그녀들의 눈빛을 보면 말이지,
아주 기대에 부푼 눈빛이 역력해
this hopeful look,
hopeful that he'll date them,
그가 자기들과 데이트
해줄 거라는 기대감,
그가 연락할 거라는 기대감,
그와 만날 수 있다는 기대감..
hopeful that he'll call them,
that he'll touch them...
and in those moments when
those same women think
그리고 이런 순간에는 다들
탈출에 대해서 생각을 하지
they're going to escape,
they get that same hopeful look
그들의 눈을 보면
항상 눈빛이 똑같애
in their eyes, except this time
they're looking at me.
나를 쳐다볼 때만 빼고 말이지
그래, 어서, 좋아
됐어, 잡았어, 어서
Yeah, come on, yeah.
You got it, you got it, come on.
어서...
Come on...
안돼!
No!
제발, 아, 안돼, 안돼!
Please-- aah, no, no!
안돼, 제발!
No, no!
And I know it's
the very last time
근데 난 그녀들이
날 그런 식으로 볼 때가
그들의 최후의 순간이라는 걸 알아
they will ever look
that way again.
The very last.
최후의 순간이지
안돼, 안돼!
No, no!
Oh, my God,
오, 맙소사
안돼, 안돼!
no, no!
그건 제가 벌써 말씀드렸잖아요
I told you about that already.
앨리슨이었어요
걔는 우리의 시녀였어요
That was Allison;
She was our server.
기억 안 나세요?
- 정신나간 커플이구만
Don't you remember?
Talk about a couple of crazies.
자기들의 결혼생활을 유지하려고 그 많은 여자들을 죽인거야?
Felt like they needed
to kill those women
to save their marriage?
아이러니가 따로 없죠
It's kind of ironic.
제 말은, 그들의 관계에서
데니스를 보호하려고 했던
I mean, the relationship
that Dennis was protecting
행동이 확실히 그를 병들어가게
만들었다는 거에요
was exactly the thing
that was making him sick.
그게 무슨 말이지?
What do you mean?
그건, 미셸이 그들의 관계에서
주도적인 역할을 했다는 거죠
I mean, Michelle's the dominant
in the relationship.
데니스는 기본적으로
대리인의 역할을 한 거고요
Dennis was basically
crazy by proxy.
그렇다면 광기도
전염된다는 말을 하는건가?
So you're saying
insanity is contagious?
Yeah, in some instances.
네, 그런 사례가 있어요
그걸 둘이서 공유하는
감응성 정신병이라고 하죠
It's called folie a deux--
madness shared by two.
정신의학적 증후군으로
It's a psychiatric syndrome
where delusional, violent
behavior is transferred
망상에 사로잡히거나,
폭력적 행동이
한 개인으로부터
다른사람으로 전이되고
from one individual
to another--
a codependency
to the nth degree.
극도로 상호의존적 성향을 보이죠
가끔은 그런 사람들이 이혼하고 나면
제정신을 찾는 경우도 있다더군요
Oftentimes
when you separate the pair,
the secondary regains
their sanity.
글쎄, 이렇게 말하고 싶군,
내가 만약에 그 남자 였다면
Well, I can tell you this--
if I did what that man did,
난 제정신 차리고 싶지 않을거야
I don't think
I'd want my sanity back.
Michelle, there are
미셸, 이 박스에서
손톱이 열 개나 나왔어요
ten fingernails in this box.
제가 말씀드렸잖아요..
I told you...
데니스는 아주 강력한
매력이 있었다고요
Dennis has
a very powerful aura.
We want
모든 여자들의 이름을 알려줘
the names of every single one
of those women.
걔네 이름 따위가 무슨 상관이죠?
What does it matter
what their names are?
They're dead.
벌써 다 죽었는걸요
It's not about them.
걔네들은 알바 아니잖아요
They're not even here.
여기 있지도 않고요
미셸, 누가 당신을 떠난거지?
Michelle... who left you?
Who was it?
그게 누굴까?
Everyone.
모두들요
They all left me.
다들 절 버렸어요
Sync by n17t01
www.addic7ed.com